Ubu Repertory Theater Script Collection ca. 1982-1994 MSS 120 MSS.120
Fales Library and Special Collections
- Series I: French Manuscripts
  - Kaminski, Patrice. 'L'ge perdu', undated; 31142040610316 (Box I.12, Folder 470)
  - Karim, Thiam Abdul. 'Ramses II, le negre', undated; 31142040610316 (Box I.12, Folder 471)
  - Kathemo, Victor. 'Le train de belle vie', undated; 31142040610316 (Box I.12, Folder 472)
  - K, Mbaye Gana. 'Deux poids et deux measures', undated; 31142040610316 (Box I.12, Folder 473)
  - K, Mbaye Gana. 'La prix de la survie', undated; 31142040610316 (Box I.12, Folder 474)
  - Keer, Jonathan. 'Le couple sur la piste', undated; 31142040610316 (Box I.12, Folder 475)
  - Keineg, Paol. '(Manque d)'aventures en Patagonie', undated; 31142040610316 (Box I.12, Folder 476)
  - Keineg, Paol. 'La reine de la nuit', undated; 31142040610316 (Box I.12, Folder 477)
  - Kemper, Stanislas. 'Le boucher jumeau blond', undated; 31142040610316 (Box I.12, Folder 478)
  - Kervan, Marcel. 'Dracula-waltz', undated; 31142040610316 (Box I.12, Folder 479)
  - KhazraParviz. 'Journal d'une marionette', undated; 31142040610316 (Box I.12, Folder 480)
  - Khaldoun, Iman. 'L'histoire inachev, undated; 31142040610316 (Box I.12, Folder 481)
  - Klein, Martial. 'Hypathie', undated; 31142040610324 (Box I.13, Folder 482)
  - Klein, Martial. 'Il est mort ton che', undated; 31142040610324 (Box I.13, Folder 483)
  - Koffi, Tiburce. 'Le paradis infernal', undated; 31142040610324 (Box I.13, Folder 484)
  - Kolt Bernard-Marie. 'Dans la solitude des champs de cotton', undated; 31142040610324 (Box I.13, Folder 485)
  - Koulsy, Henri Lamko. 'Mon fils de mon fr', undated; 31142040610324 (Box I.13, Folder 486)
  - Koulsy, Henri Lamko. 'Ndo kala ou l'initiation avort, undated; 31142040610324 (Box I.13, Folder 487)
  - Koulsy, Henri Lamko. 'Tout bassi bas!', undated; 31142040610324 (Box I.13, Folder 488)
  - Koulsy, Henri Lamko. 'La ziggourat de Babel', undated; 31142040610324 (Box I.13, Folder 489)
  - Kreidwise, Shirley M. 'Matinor le temps des cerises', undated; 31142040610324 (Box I.13, Folder 490)
  - Kribus, Serge. 'Cagoul', undated; 31142040610324 (Box I.13, Folder 491)
  - Kribus, Serge. 'Le grand retour de Boris Speilman', undated; 31142040610324 (Box I.13, Folder 492)
  - Kristof, Agota. 'John et Joe', undated; 31142040610324 (Box I.13, Folder 492)
  - Kukawka, Pascale. 'Marie', undated; 31142040610324 (Box I.13, Folder 493)
  - KwahulKoffi. 'Cette vieille magie noire', undated; 31142040610324 (Box I.13, Folder 494)
  - KwahulKoffi. 'La dame du caf'en France', undated; 31142040610324 (Box I.13, Folder 495)
  - KwahulKoffi. 'La dame du caf'en France', undated; 31142040610324 (Box I.13, Folder 496)
  - KwahulKoffi. 'Fama', undated; 31142040610324 (Box I.13, Folder 497)
  - KwahulKoffi. 'Il nous faut l'Amque!', undated; 31142040610324 (Box I.13, Folder 498)
  - KwahulKoffi. 'Jaz', undated; 31142040610324 (Box I.13, Folder 499)
  - La Combe, Jean Pol. 'Drts', undated; 31142040610324 (Box I.13, Folder 500)
  - Lagarce, Jean-Luc. 'Derniers remords avant l'oubli', undated; 31142040610324 (Box I.13, Folder 501)
  - Lagarce, Jean-Luc. 'Music-Hall', undated; 31142040610324 (Box I.13, Folder 502)
  - Lagarce, Jean-Luc. 'Les serviteurs', undated; 31142040610324 (Box I.13, Folder 503)
  - Lagrave, Jean-Paul de. 'Un volcan sous la neige', undated; 31142040610324 (Box I.13, Folder 504)
  - Lahmar, Rachid. 'L'echelle de l'ascension', undated; 31142040610324 (Box I.13, Folder 505)
  - Laison, Amah Osseh. 'Le miroir', undated; 31142040610324 (Box I.13, Folder 506)
  - Lam, Parina and Laurent, Pascal. 'Nom d'un chien!', undated; 31142040610324 (Box I.13, Folder 507)
  - Lambert, Lucien. 'Les Charlottes', undated; 31142040610324 (Box I.13, Folder 508)
  - Lamblin, Philippe. 'Asumpta et Felix sont dans un bateau', undated; 31142040610324 (Box I.13, Folder 509)
  - Lamorlette, Christiane. 'Persistance des protocloches', undated; 31142040610324 (Box I.13, Folder 510)
  - Laou, Julius Ame. 'Une autre histoire ou le malentendu', undated; 31142040610324 (Box I.13, Folder 511)
  - Laou, Julius Am. 'Ne m'appelez jamais ne!', undated; 31142040610324 (Box I.13, Folder 512)
  - Laplante, Marie-Line. 'Le couteau et la bouche', undated; 31142040610324 (Box I.13, Folder 513)
  - Laplante, Marie-Line. 'L'homme assis', undated; 31142040610324 (Box I.13, Folder 514)
  - Lasquin, Christiane. 'Attention a p'tite marche', undated; 31142040610324 (Box I.13, Folder 515)
  - Lasry, Philippe. 'Journ suspendues', undated; 31142040610324 (Box I.13, Folder 516)
  - Lassaille, Claire. 'L'un l'autre', undated; 31142040610324 (Box I.13, Folder 517)
  - Lassaille, Claire. 'Mnippe ou la voix de la nuit', undated; 31142040610324 (Box I.13, Folder 518)
  - Laureillard, R. 'Sade en ', undated; 31142040610324 (Box I.13, Folder 519)
  - Laurent, Pascal and Lam, Parina. 'Remords vivants', undated; 31142040610324 (Box I.13, Folder 520)
  - Lavie, Dre. 'Vivement la guerre! (Adolf et Neumann)', undated; 31142040610332 (Box I.14, Folder 521)
  - Leal, Odile Pedro. 'La chanson de philibert ou les gens simples', undated; 31142040610332 (Box I.14, Folder 522)
  - Lebeau, Philippe. 'Et tout en bas, la ville', undated; 31142040610332 (Box I.14, Folder 523)
  - Lebeau, Yves. 'La crieuse', undated; 31142040610332 (Box I.14, Folder 524)
  - Lebeau, Yves. 'Une maison sous les drapes de lin', undated; 31142040610332 (Box I.14, Folder 525)
  - Le Cam, Gerard. 'La haute mer n'existe plus', undated; 31142040610332 (Box I.14, Folder 526)
  - Leconte, Frantz Antoine. 'La rblique', undated; 31142040610332 (Box I.14, Folder 527)
  - Legault, Anne. 'La visite des sauvages ou l' en forme de t de vache', undated; 31142040610332 (Box I.14, Folder 528)
  - Le Gouic, Laurence. 'Interieur atelier', undated; 31142040610332 (Box I.14, Folder 529)
  - Leite-Lopes, Angela. 'Ariane', undated; 31142040610332 (Box I.14, Folder 530)
  - Leite-Lopes, Angela. 'Le chant de la mer', undated; 31142040610332 (Box I.14, Folder 531)
  - Lejeune, Didier. 'Le paradoxe de Zn', undated; 31142040610332 (Box I.14, Folder 532)
  - Lemae, Maurice. 'L'amour en frans', undated; 31142040610332 (Box I.14, Folder 533)
  - Lemae, Maurice. 'L'ascension du Phx M.B.', undated; 31142040610332 (Box I.14, Folder 534)
  - Lemae, Maurice. 'Le boudoir de la philosophie', undated; 31142040610332 (Box I.14, Folder 535)
  - Lemae, Maurice. 'Le boulevard du surrisme', undated; 31142040610332 (Box I.14, Folder 536)
  - Lemae, Maurice. 'Filmography de Maurice Lemae', undated; 31142040610332 (Box I.14, Folder 537)
  - Lemae, Maurice. 'Krh', undated; 31142040610332 (Box I.14, Folder 538)
  - Lemae, Maurice. 'Pour un thre neuf', undated; 31142040610332 (Box I.14, Folder 539)
  - Lemae, Maurice. 'Socrate jugar Esculape', undated; 31142040610332 (Box I.14, Folder 540)
  - Lemae, Maurice. 'Le thre futuriste italien et russe', undated; 31142040610332 (Box I.14, Folder 541)
  - Lemieux, Pierre-Yves. 'Monsieur Smytchkov et Madame Smytchkov', undated; 31142040610332 (Box I.14, Folder 542)
  - Lemoine, Jean-Ren'L'odeur du noir', undated; 31142040610332 (Box I.14, Folder 543)
  - Lengliney, Michel. 'La violoncelliste', undated; 31142040610332 (Box I.14, Folder 544)
  - Lepeu, Monick. 'Gertrude morte cet aprmidi', undated; 31142040610332 (Box I.14, Folder 545)
  - Le Prince, Pierre Yves. 'Le saut de la mort', undated; 31142040610332 (Box I.14, Folder 545)
  - Leplus, Franck. 'Sacrs! ou Js de Rigobert', undated; 31142040610332 (Box I.14, Folder 546)
  - Lepoutre, Raymond. 'Moi, l'Amque', undated; 31142040610332 (Box I.14, Folder 547)
  - Lerebours, Michel-Philippe. 'Les circoncis de la Saint Jean', undated; 31142040610332 (Box I.14, Folder 548)
  - Lescure, Pierre. 'Jacob ou le combat contre dieu', undated; 31142040610332 (Box I.14, Folder 549)
  - Lescure, Pierre. 'Luridon', undated; 31142040610332 (Box I.14, Folder 550)
  - Levick, Hugh. 'Kid Copy', undated; 31142040610332 (Box I.14, Folder 551)
  - Levy-Marie, Catherine. 'Femmes entre parentheses', undated; 31142040610332 (Box I.14, Folder 552)
  - Levy, Lorraine. 'Zelda ou le masque', undated; 31142040610332 (Box I.14, Folder 553)
  - Lewis, Martin. 'La fleche du Parthe', undated; 31142040610332 (Box I.14, Folder 554)
  - Lhomme, Michel. 'Sous pression (ou esa tierra es mi corazon)', undated; 31142040610332 (Box I.14, Folder 555)
  - Liaz. 'Le parie de Dizo', undated; 31142040610332 (Box I.14, Folder 556)
  - Liking, Werewere. 'Heros d'eau', undated; 31142040610332 (Box I.14, Folder 557)
  - Liking, Werewere. 'La veuve diyilem', undated; 31142040610332 (Box I.14, Folder 558)
  - Lombardo, Alberto. 'Longtemps nous nous sommes reveilles avec un mal de crane', undated; 31142040610332 (Box I.14, Folder 559)
  - Lombardo, Alberto. 'Un parfum de Montgolfi', undated; 31142040610332 (Box I.14, Folder 560)
  - Lounes, Abderrahmane. 'Journal d'une femme de meninges', undated; 31142040610332 (Box I.14, Folder 561)
  - Louvet, Jean. 'Un faust', undated; 31142040610332 (Box I.14, Folder 562)
  - Lyelh, Nicolas. 'La balle perdu', undated; 31142040610340 (Box I.15, Folder 563)
  - Lynx, Hugo. 'Bonne route!', undated; 31142040610340 (Box I.15, Folder 564)
  - MacJacques. 'Les gourmands', undated; 31142040610340 (Box I.15, Folder 565)
  - MacJacques. 'Le paradis sur terre', undated; 31142040610340 (Box I.15, Folder 566)
  - Madani, Ahmed. 'Rapt', undated; 31142040610340 (Box I.15, Folder 567)
  - Madingo, Tawite. 'Echec aux cannibales', undated; 31142040610340 (Box I.15, Folder 568)
  - Magloire, Franck. 'La lecture de la lettre', undated; 31142040610340 (Box I.15, Folder 569)
  - Magnin, Jean-Daniel. 'Est-ce qu'il fait nuit sur le soleil?', undated; 31142040610340 (Box I.15, Folder 570)
  - Magnien, Raynald. 'Y'a pas de quoi en faire un drame', undated; 31142040610340 (Box I.15, Folder 571)
  - Magny, Mich. 'Le dernier rose aux jones', undated; 31142040610340 (Box I.15, Folder 572)
  - Makhele, Caya. 'La fable du cloitre des cimetis', undated; 31142040610340 (Box I.15, Folder 573)
  - Makhele, Caya. 'Le petit matin', undated; 31142040610340 (Box I.15, Folder 574)
  - Makhele, Caya. 'Picpus', undated; 31142040610340 (Box I.15, Folder 575)
  - Malabat, Grd. 'Passio', undated; 31142040610340 (Box I.15, Folder 576)
  - Malela, Louya Mpene. 'L'homo-regnum', undated; 31142040610340 (Box I.15, Folder 577)
  - Mallat, Robert. 'Nuremberg 96', undated; 31142040610340 (Box I.15, Folder 578)
  - Malraux, Alain. 'Pentac, undated; 31142040610340 (Box I.15, Folder 579)
  - Manet, Edouardo. 'Les nonnes', undated; 31142040610340 (Box I.15, Folder 580)
  - Manet, Edouardo. 'Pour l'amour de Verdi', undated; 31142040610340 (Box I.15, Folder 581)
  - Manet, Edouardo. 'Un soir de Tartuffe', undated; 31142040610340 (Box I.15, Folder 582)
  - Marc, Patrice. 'o', undated; 31142040610340 (Box I.15, Folder 583)
  - Marcellin, Marianne. 'En toute intimit/unittitle>, undated; 31142040610340 (Box I.15, Folder 584)
  - Marcellin, Marianne. 'Permis de sejours', undated; 31142040610340 (Box I.15, Folder 585)
  - Marcellin, Marianne. 'Rideau!', undated; 31142040610340 (Box I.15, Folder 586)
  - Marchica, Ettore. 'Il n'y a jamais du toujours', undated; 31142040610340 (Box I.15, Folder 587)
  - Marinier, Robert. 'L'insomnie', undated; 31142040610340 (Box I.15, Folder 588)
  - Marland, Serge. 'Juliette du Toboso', undated; 31142040610340 (Box I.15, Folder 589)
  - Marsot, Marie-France. 'La deuxi ligne', undated; 31142040610340 (Box I.15, Folder 590)
  - Martin-Fuguier, Jean-Paul. 'Olympe et la guillotine', undated; 31142040610340 (Box I.15, Folder 591)
  - Martin, Lise. 'Zones rouges', undated; 31142040610340 (Box I.15, Folder 592)
  - Mathias, Bernard and Leymarie, Genevi. 'Blasphs', undated; 31142040610340 (Box I.15, Folder 593)
  - Maura, Carlos Semprun. 'Le bleu de l'eau-de-vie', undated; 31142040610340 (Box I.15, Folder 594)
  - Matz, Charles. 'Antonin Artaud: le soleil noir', undated; 31142040610340 (Box I.15, Folder 595)
  - Mawo, Tingayama [aka Malin, Juno]. 'Promrecherch/unittitle>, undated; 31142040610340 (Box I.15, Folder 596)
  - Maz, Bernard. 'On a feulhez Mr Sloop', undated; 31142040610340 (Box I.15, Folder 597)
  - Mazouz. 'Silence', undated; 31142040610340 (Box I.15, Folder 598)
  - M'baye, Aby. 'Le chapeau', undated; 31142040610340 (Box I.15, Folder 599)
  - McCracken, Elisabeth. 'Le complexe de Laios', undated; 31142040610340 (Box I.15, Folder 600)
  - Medard, Lemina Remy. 'Un long r sterile', undated; 31142040610340 (Box I.15, Folder 601)
  - Meddeb, Abdelwahab. 'La gazelle et l'enfant', undated; 31142040610340 (Box I.15, Folder 602)
  - Mehenni, Hocine. 'Les coquelicots', undated; 31142040610340 (Box I.15, Folder 603)
  - Mani, Hamma. 'L'ange violent', undated; 31142040610357 (Box I.16, Folder 604)
  - Mani, Hamma. 'Demence, les trois saisons', undated; 31142040610357 (Box I.16, Folder 605)
  - Mani, Hamma. 'Massajine', undated; 31142040610357 (Box I.16, Folder 606)
  - Mani, Hamma. 'Le vent de la demence', undated; 31142040610357 (Box I.16, Folder 607)
  - Mani, Hamma. 'Virage violent', undated; 31142040610357 (Box I.16, Folder 608)
  - Melite, Luce. 'Drdres', undated; 31142040610357 (Box I.16, Folder 609)
  - Melquiot, Frabrice. 'Le jardin de Beamon', undated; 31142040610357 (Box I.16, Folder 610)
  - Mezoughi, R. 'Mdres de l'l', undated; 31142040610357 (Box I.16, Folder 611)
  - Micone, Marco. 'Addolorata', undated; 31142040610357 (Box I.16, Folder 612)
  - Mignot, Jacques. 'Bonsoir genus', undated; 31142040610357 (Box I.16, Folder 613)
  - Milin, Gildas. 'L'ordalie', undated; 31142040610357 (Box I.16, Folder 614)
  - Milin, Gildas. 'Le triomphe de l'echec', undated; 31142040610357 (Box I.16, Folder 615)
  - Milin, Gildas. 'Le triomphe de l'echec', undated; 31142040610357 (Box I.16, Folder 616)
  - Milovanoff, Jean-Pierre. 'Cinquante mille nuits d'amour', undated; 31142040610357 (Box I.16, Folder 617)
  - Milovanoff, Jean-Pierre. 'Le roi d'Islande', undated; 31142040610357 (Box I.16, Folder 618)
  - Minyana, Philippe. 'Exposition', undated; 31142040610357 (Box I.16, Folder 619)
  - Monga, Lolita. 'Le cercle', undated; 31142040610357 (Box I.16, Folder 620)
  - Mongo, Pab'Le philosophe et le sorcier', undated; 31142040610357 (Box I.16, Folder 621)
  - Mongo, Pab'Un totem de plus', undated; 31142040610357 (Box I.16, Folder 622)
  - Monsarrat, Cne. 'Adieu Monsieur Tchekov', undated; 31142040610357 (Box I.16, Folder 623)
  - Montantin, Mich. 'Vie et mort de Vaval', undated; 31142040610357 (Box I.16, Folder 624)
  - Moratal, Marcel. 'Petit a et petit b', undated; 31142040610357 (Box I.16, Folder 625)
  - Moreau, Isabelle. 'L'acteur studieux ou le r de Kattie', undated; 31142040610357 (Box I.16, Folder 626)
  - Moreau, Isabelle. 'Le meilleur ami', undated; 31142040610357 (Box I.16, Folder 627)
  - Moreau, Jacky. 'Ici', undated; 31142040610357 (Box I.16, Folder 628)
  - Moreau, Jacky. 'La sage-femme et le fossoyeur', undated; 31142040610357 (Box I.16, Folder 629)
  - Moro, Marc. 'Le cancer des mots', undated; 31142040610357 (Box I.16, Folder 630)
  - Mouawad, Wajdi. 'Journde noces chez les Cromagnons', undated; 31142040610357 (Box I.16, Folder 631)
  - Mouawad, Wajdi. 'Les mains d'Edwige au moment de la naissance', undated; 31142040610357 (Box I.16, Folder 632)
  - Moussa, Konate. 'Le dernier pas', undated; 31142040610357 (Box I.16, Folder 633)
  - Mudaba, Yoka Lye. 'Miarame ou les animaux maladies de la faim', undated; 31142040610357 (Box I.16, Folder 634)
  - Mujomba, Pierre Mumbere. 'La derni enveloppe (first version)', undated; 31142040610357 (Box I.16, Folder 635)
  - Mujomba, Pierre Mumbere. 'La derni enveloppe', undated; 31142040610357 (Box I.16, Folder 636)
  - Munga, Moma. 'Les deux extremit, undated; 31142040610357 (Box I.16, Folder 637)
  - Musala, Nzey van. 'Tanganyka, le viol du tabernacle', undated; 31142040610357 (Box I.16, Folder 638)
  - Musangi Ntemo, Paul-Olivier. 'Le pacte de Ntu', undated; 31142040610357 (Box I.16, Folder 639)
  - Nabulsi, Layla. 'Debout les morts!', undated; 31142040610357 (Box I.16, Folder 640)
  - Nadaus, Roland. 'Oh, quand les saints', undated; 31142040610357 (Box I.16, Folder 641)
  - Nadeau, Michel. '14 aoisque le monde bouge', undated; 31142040610357 (Box I.16, Folder 642)
  - Nadouce, Philippe. 'La ferraille', undated; 31142040610365 (Box I.17, Folder 643)
  - Nadouce, Philippe. 'Les rivis', undated; 31142040610365 (Box I.17, Folder 644)
  - Namiand, Arlette. 'Abonnabsents', undated; 31142040610365 (Box I.17, Folder 645)
  - Namiand, Arlette. 'Surtout quand la nuit tombe', undated; 31142040610365 (Box I.17, Folder 646)
  - Namiand, Arlette. 'Les yeux d'encre', undated; 31142040610365 (Box I.17, Folder 647)
  - Nataf, Andr'L'embarquement pour Cyth', undated; 31142040610365 (Box I.17, Folder 648)
  - Ndiaye, Sada Weinde. 'Le pari de l'ancien', undated; 31142040610365 (Box I.17, Folder 649)
  - N'debeka, Maxime. 'L'arbre outeilles', undated; 31142040610365 (Box I.17, Folder 650)
  - N'debeka, Maxime. 'Le destin de l'immortel fouabiss', undated; 31142040610365 (Box I.17, Folder 651)
  - N'debeka, Maxime. 'Equatorium', undated; 31142040610365 (Box I.17, Folder 652)
  - Ndedi Penda, Patrice. 'Le char des dieux', undated; 31142040610365 (Box I.17, Folder 653)
  - Ndjekery, Noel Netonon. 'Feu et flame', undated; 31142040610365 (Box I.17, Folder 654)
  - Ndjekery, Noel Netonon. 'Goudangou', undated; 31142040610365 (Box I.17, Folder 655)
  - Nicloux, Guillaume. 'Les grenouilles', undated; 31142040610365 (Box I.17, Folder 656)
  - Niedzwiecki, Patricia. 'Madame Antoine', undated; 31142040610365 (Box I.17, Folder 657)
  - Nilly, Yves. 'Remarques sur l'horizon et ses habitants', undated; 31142040610365 (Box I.17, Folder 658)
  - Njock, Manuna Ma. 'Orphd'Afrique', undated; 31142040610365 (Box I.17, Folder 659)
  - Nocher, Frans. 'Tchekhov Tchekhova', undated; 31142040610365 (Box I.17, Folder 660)
  - No Annie. 'Anatole', undated; 31142040610365 (Box I.17, Folder 661)
  - Nonneville, Emmanuel de. 'La chant de Perlamer', undated; 31142040610365 (Box I.17, Folder 662)
  - Nordmann, Gabriel. 'La mangeuse de crottes', undated; 31142040610365 (Box I.17, Folder 663)
  - Northcott, Richard. 'Ville lumi ou parler dans le noir', undated; 31142040610365 (Box I.17, Folder 664)
  - N'tumb, Diur. 'Za', undated; 31142040610365 (Box I.17, Folder 665)
  - N'tumb, Diur. 'Qui hurle dans la nuit?', undated; 31142040610365 (Box I.17, Folder 666)
  - Nuzzo, Sebastien. 'La finale', undated; 31142040610365 (Box I.17, Folder 667)
  - Nysenholc, Adolphe. 'Kammerspiel', undated; 31142040610365 (Box I.17, Folder 668)
  - Nysenholc, Adolphe. 'Survive ou la mire blanche', undated; 31142040610365 (Box I.17, Folder 669)
  - Nzola-Meso M., Dr. Emmanuel. 'Fnin, masculin et singulier', undated; 31142040610365 (Box I.17, Folder 670)
  - Obadia, Bernard. 'Nuits', undated; 31142040610365 (Box I.17, Folder 671)
  - Obadia, Bernard. 'Pour le moment', undated; 31142040610365 (Box I.17, Folder 672)
  - Olmi, Vnique. 'Le passage', undated; 31142040610365 (Box I.17, Folder 673)
  - Ortega, Bernard. 'Fantdu soir', undated; 31142040610365 (Box I.17, Folder 674)
  - Orville, Xavier. 'Bergamotte et Anatole, la romance', undated; 31142040610365 (Box I.17, Folder 675)
  - Ouerghi, Noureddine. 'La trage des coqs', undated; 31142040610365 (Box I.17, Folder 676)
  - Owondo, Laurent. 'La folle du gouverneur', undated; 31142040610365 (Box I.17, Folder 677)
  - Oyono-Mbia, Guillaume. 'Le bourbier', undated; 31142040610365 (Box I.17, Folder 678)
  - Palustran, Christian. 'Un papillon jaune appelphinx', undated; 31142040610373 (Box I.18, Folder 679)
  - Pambou, Frric. 'Grosso-modo', undated; 31142040610373 (Box I.18, Folder 680)
  - Panijel, Jacques. 'Carmel n 18', undated; 31142040610373 (Box I.18, Folder 681)
  - Panijel, Jacques. 'Nicht nur ein berliner', undated; 31142040610373 (Box I.18, Folder 682)
  - Parenteau-Lebeuf, Dominick. 'Dilement devant notaire', undated; 31142040610373 (Box I.18, Folder 683)
  - Parenteau-Lebeuf, Dominick. 'Po pour une nuit d'anniversaire', undated; 31142040610373 (Box I.18, Folder 684)
  - Parisot, Francis. 'Dominique ou la belle vie', undated; 31142040610373 (Box I.18, Folder 685)
  - Pascarel, Charles. 'Le strage del vuoto', undated; 31142040610373 (Box I.18, Folder 686)
  - Passerrat, Jean. '(In)certitudes', undated; 31142040610373 (Box I.18, Folder 687)
  - Pelaez, Jean-Pierre. 'Les explorateurs', undated; 31142040610373 (Box I.18, Folder 688)
  - Pelletier, Beno 'Le saut de l'ange', undated; 31142040610373 (Box I.18, Folder 689)
  - Pelletier, Pol. 'Joie', undated; 31142040610373 (Box I.18, Folder 690)
  - Pellier, Isabelle. 'Touche-touche', undated; 31142040610373 (Box I.18, Folder 691)
  - Pelsy-Johann, Eric. 'En avant le cirque', undated; 31142040610373 (Box I.18, Folder 692)
  - Pereira, Manuel Antonio. 'The', undated; 31142040610373 (Box I.18, Folder 693)
  - Perrier, Olivier. 'Des sies de paix', undated; 31142040610373 (Box I.18, Folder 694)
  - Perry, Jacques. 'De l'importance d'e aim, undated; 31142040610373 (Box I.18, Folder 695)
  - Perry, Jacques. 'Trilogue', undated; 31142040610373 (Box I.18, Folder 696)
  - Petit, Marie. 'Dacements', undated; 31142040610373 (Box I.18, Folder 697)
  - Petit, Marie. 'Territoires', undated; 31142040610373 (Box I.18, Folder 698)
  - Petit-Delisle, Serge-Edouard. Deux-dingue ou l'histoire de Charles-Edmond Duchene', undated; 31142040610373 (Box I.18, Folder 699)
  - Peycherand, Hne. 'Le son d'un bruit', undated; 31142040610373 (Box I.18, Folder 700)
  - Philip, Michel. 'Deuil', undated; 31142040610373 (Box I.18, Folder 701)
  - Philip, Michel. 'Doosita ou les charmes mortels de la tyrannie', undated; 31142040610373 (Box I.18, Folder 702)
  - Philip, Michel. 'Les plaisirs scrats de la vieillesse', undated; 31142040610373 (Box I.18, Folder 703)
  - Picq, Jean-Yves. 'Le contrat des attachements', undated; 31142040610373 (Box I.18, Folder 704)
  - Picq, Jean-Yves. 'De la dlition comme art et comme projet', undated; 31142040610373 (Box I.18, Folder 705)
  - Picq, Jean-Yves. 'Vos ou le retour d'Ulysse', undated; 31142040610373 (Box I.18, Folder 706)
  - Piemme, Jean-Marie. 'Les forts, les faibles', undated; 31142040610373 (Box I.18, Folder 707)
  - Pilate, Pascal. 'Mise amour', undated; 31142040610373 (Box I.18, Folder 708)
  - Pliya, Jos'Black Wanderings', undated; 31142040610373 (Box I.18, Folder 709)
  - Pliya, Jos'La conspiration', undated; 31142040610373 (Box I.18, Folder 710)
  - Pliya, Jos'Mires d'Anophele', undated; 31142040610373 (Box I.18, Folder 711)
  - Pliya, Jos'Negrerrances', undated; 31142040610373 (Box I.18, Folder 712)
  - Poissant, Claude. 'Passer la nuit', undated; 31142040610373 (Box I.18, Folder 713)
  - Poli, Jean-Laurent and Ledee, Duke. 'Compte bloqu/unittitle>, undated; 31142040610373 (Box I.18, Folder 714)
  - Pontary, Lina. 'Les dames des quatre chemins', undated; 31142040610373 (Box I.18, Folder 715)
  - Pontcharra, Natacha de. 'Cet assassin la vous aime', undated; 31142040610373 (Box I.18, Folder 716)
  - Pontcharra, Natacha de. 'Le trempe', undated; 31142040610373 (Box I.18, Folder 717)
  - Prnt, Henri. 'Mister Amour', undated; 31142040610373 (Box I.18, Folder 718)
  - Pressman, Elie. 'Le jour et la nuit', undated; 31142040610381 (Box I.19, Folder 719)
  - Pressman, Elie. 'Si vous n'aimez pas le violon', undated; 31142040610381 (Box I.19, Folder 720)
  - Pressman, Elie. 'Parlez-moi d'amour', undated; 31142040610381 (Box I.19, Folder 721)
  - Pressman, Elie. 'L'oisellerie', undated; 31142040610381 (Box I.19, Folder 722)
  - Pressman, Elie. 'La solitude de l'oeuf avant l'omelette', undated; 31142040610381 (Box I.19, Folder 723)
  - Pressman, Elie. 'L'autre', undated; 31142040610381 (Box I.19, Folder 724)
  - Provost, Martin. 'Les poup', undated; 31142040610381 (Box I.19, Folder 725)
  - Provost, Martin. 'Le voyage immobile', undated; 31142040610381 (Box I.19, Folder 726)